[Music]
My special wife and I have been living
in this government-provided quarter with our children for many
years.
With time, my children are growing up in
this house. Our
dream is to have our own house. Even if it's
not big enough, it should be enough for me to
live with my family in comfort and happiness. To fulfill this dream, I
need a reliable plan.
A trusted name will support you in fulfilling all your responsibilities. ICICI
Prudential Life. We bring you a
new-age plan: ICICI Prudential
Life. You will receive a
large corpus at a fixed time, so you can
fulfill your biggest dreams.
With ICICI Prudential Life, you
too can fulfill your dreams like Vijay Bhandari. The
lumpsum option of this plan offers you many
benefits. By paying a premium of Rs. 50,000 every year for 10 years,
you will accumulate a large corpus after 20 years. When the
policy matures,
you will receive tax-free funds,
which you can use for a bright future for you and your family.
You are also protected with life cover for
your future and your
growing needs throughout the policy term.  Choose ICICI Russia Sukh
Samriddhi that gives you the
assurance of guaranteed returns and bonus growth opportunities
through a preferential life insurance that supports you in all your dreams
[Music]